Finding Aid for Blair Moody Papers 1928-1954
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Visual Materials
  - Motion Pictures
    - Miscellaneous FIlms
      - Prisoners of war and Korean cease fire; Senators: Long, Morse, Dworshak, and Know, undated; 8634-29
        - Streaming File: 8634-29, flash-flv
Apr. 1, 1946, Dec 19, 1947, Apr. 19, 1949, May 21, 1951, July 25, 1952
Forrestal, James, 1892-1949.
Apr. 16, 1946, Mar. 16, 1948
Frear, Joseph Allen, 1903-
May 7, 1951
Fruehauf, Harvey Charles, 1893-
May 10, 1938
Fulbright, J. William (James William), 1905-
Jan. 11, 1952
Gannett, Frank E. (Frank Ernest), 1876-1957.
Sept. 6, 1944
George, Walter F. (Walter Franklin), 1878-1957.
Jan. 30, 1952
Green, Thoedore Francis, 1867-
Mar. 5, 1933, Apr. 24, 1952
Green, William, 1870-1952.
Aug. 1, 1951, Apr. 18, 1952
Griffiths, Hicks G., 1910-
Mar. 26, 1951, Apr. 13, 1951, May 12, 1951, May 24, 1951, June 8, 1951
Hannah, John A., 1902-
Mar. 20, 1951, Apr. 11, 1952
Harmon, Tom.
June 1, 1951
Henderson, Leon, 1895-
Apr. 17, 1941
Herlong, Albert Sydney, 1909-
May 28., 1952
Hersey, John, 1914-
July 1, 1947
Herter, Christian Archibald, 1895-1966.
Jan. 19, 1948
Hill, Norman Llewellyn, 1895-
June 24.1934, May 10, 1935, Aug. 12, 1935, Aug. 27, 1935, Jan. 14, 1936, Feb. 25, 1936, Apr. 2.1936, Nov.6, 1952
Hoey, Clyde Roark, 1877-1954.
June 8, 1951, Jan. 10, 1952
Hoffman, Clare Eugene, 1875-1967.
Apr. 24, 1942
Hoffman, Paul G. (Paul Gray), 1891-1974
May 2, 1939, .Feb. 21, 1942, Feb. 23, 1943, Mar. 20, 1943.June 30, 1944, Nov. 29, 1944, Aug. 26, 1945 [about], Sept. 26, 1946, Dec. 16, 1946, Apr. 1, 1947, Oct. 3, 1949, Oct. 13, 1949, Feb. 8, 1950, Feb. 18, 1950, Oct- 1950 [with Hoffman European mission], Oct. 30, 1951, Feb. 28, 1952
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.
Dec. 31, 1949 (Hoover to William F. Knowland)
Hoover, J. Edgar (John Edgar), 1895-1972
June 26, 1943, Jan. 14, 1952
Hopkins, Harry Lloyd 1890-1946.
Dec. 8, 1937
Humphrey, Hubert H. (Hubert Horatio), 1911-1978
Apr. 26, 1949, May 31, 1950, Jan. 14, 1952, Mar. 18, 1952, Mar. 25, 1952, Aug. 27, 1952, Nov. 8, 1952
Ives, Irving McNeil, 1896-
Nov. 21, 1927
Johnson, Louis Arthur, 1891-
May 16, 1949, Aug. 16, 1949, Oct. 14, 1949, Apr. 14, 1950
Johnson, Lyndon B. (Lyndon Baines), 1908-1973
June 12,1951 (encl.), July 19, 1951, July 27, 1951, Sept. 24, 1951, Dec. 28, 1951, Mar. 25, 1952
Johnson, Pyke
Jan. 29, 1942, Feb. 6, 1942
Johnston, Eric A. (Eric Allen), 1895-1963
Apr. 15, 1947, Aug.12, 1947
Kaiser, Edgar Fosburg, 1908-
Mar. 20, 1952 (encl.), July 17, 1952 (encl.)
Kefauver, Estes, 1903-1963.
Aug. 23.1949, May 14.1951 (encl. with letter of June 12, 1951), Aug. 20, 1951, June 11, 1952, Aug. 5, 1952, Aug. 18, 1952, Nov. 25, 1952
Kennedy, John F. (John Fitzgerald), 1917-1963.
Mar. 10, 1942
Kerr, Robert S. (Robert Samuel), 1896-1963.
Apr. 25, 1951, June 11, 1952
Kirchwey, Freda
Mar. 14, 1952
Knowland, Helen Davis Herrick
Jan. 31, 1946
Knowland, William Fife,1908-
Nov. 13, 1945 (Knowland to Schwellenback concerning inflation), Aug. 13, 1946, Jan. 14, 1952, Aug. 16, 1946
Knudsen, William S., 1879-1948.
Nov. 24, 1941
Labor
1938 and 1945-1946 concerning unions, strikes, and the National Labor Relations Board
Lamont, Thomas Stilwell, 1899-
Jan. 21, 1936, Feb. 10, 1936, Feb. 13, 1936
Langer, William, 1886-1959
June 18, 1951
Leahy, William D 1875-1959.
May 1, 1946
Lehman, Herbert H. (Herbert Henry), 1878-1963.
July 27, 1936, June 16.1951 (encl.), Mar. 12, 1952, Apr. 23, 1952, May 5, 1952
Lenhart, Laurence G. 1893-
Throughout
Lodge, Henry Cabot, 1902-
Apr. 14, 1948, Oct. 26, 1949, Jan. 22, 1952
Lovett, Robert A. (Robert Abercrombie), 1895-
Dec. 31, 1947 (on Marshall Plan), Jan. 2, 1948
Luce, Robert Harding, 1900-
Mar. 15, 1938
McClellan, John Little, 1896-
May 16, 1951, July 10, 1951, Sept. 25, 1951
McCloy, John Jay, 1895-
Aug. 14, 1951 [memo]
McCormack, John W., 1891-
June 29, 1948, Sept. 29, 1949, 1951 [undated memo], Aug. 4, 1952 [H.L.S.], Aug. 14, 1952
McFarland, Ernest William, 1894-
Aug. 29, 1951, Oct. 1, 1951, Jan. 16, 1952, Jan. 31, 1952
McMahon, Brien, 1903-1952.
Jan. 17, 1949, May 18, 1951
Mapes, Carl Herbert, 1900-
July 6, 1938
Martin, John Butlin, 1909-
Aug. 27, 1951
Martin, Joseph William, 1884-1968
Aug. 17, 1939, Jan. 10, 1940
Monroney, Mike, 1902-
Sept. 23., 1948, Aug. 12, 1950
Morse, Wayne Lyman, 1900-
Jan. 18, 1947
Murphy, Frank 1890-1949.
Aug. 17, 1932, May 11, 1933, Mar. 13, 1936, Jan. 16, 1937, Feb. 23, 1937, Mar. 6, 1937, Feb. 28, 1938, Feb. 7, 1944, Feb. 8, 1944, Dec. 5, 1947
Murphy, George, 1897-1961.
Nov. 15, 1933, June 22, 1934, June 19, 1941
Murphy, Robert F. 1899-
Apr.1, 1952
Murray, Philip, 1886-1952.
Apr. 13, 1950
Nelson, Donald Marr, 1888-1959.
May 21, 1942, Feb. 4, 1944
O'Dwyer, William, 1890-1964
Mar 10, 1952
Owens, Henry J
May 6, 1952
Pastore, John Orlando, 1907-
Apr. 26, 1951, Feb. 12, 1952
Picard, Frank A. 1889-1963.
Nov.28, 1938, May 28, 1951 [encl. in Moody letter of June 6, 1951]
Rabaut, Louis Charles, 1886-1961
Jan. 23, 1952
Rankin, John Elliott, 1882-1962
Sept. 10, 1951
Reuther, Victor G. (Victor George), 1912-
Dec 5, 1950
Reuther Walter, 1907-1970
Oct. 17, 1942, Feb. 9, 1944, Dec. 6, 1944, Dec. 13, 1944, Mar. 29, 1946, Aug. 26, 1947, Apr. 4, 1950, June 7, 1950, May 21, 1951, Jan. 7, 1952, June 13, 1952
Reynolds, Quentin James, 1902-1965
Apr. 24, 1951
Romney, George W., 1907-
Jan.14, 1942, Feb. 11, 1942, June 30, 1942, July 1942, Oct. 19, 1942, Nov. 28, 1942, Nov. 12, 1943, Dec. 20, 1946, Apr. 7, 1952, Apr. 9, 1952
Roosevelt, Dorothy Kemp, 1899?-1985
Sept. 6, 1946
Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1884-1962.
Mar. 13, 1954
Roosevelt, Franklin Delano, 1882-1945.
Admiral Leahy [interview] discussing President Roosevelt's health
Rosenberg, Anna M. 1902-
July 21, 1936
Ruml, Beardsley, 1894-
Mar. 30, 1945
Russell, Richard B. (Richard Brevard), 1897-1971
Jan. 12, 1952
Ruthven, Alexander Grant, 1882-
June 4, 1951
Saltonstall, Leverett, 1892-
Apr. 12, 1948
Scholle, August 1904-
Aug. 9, 1951
Scripps, Edward Wyllis, 1909-
Apr. 19, 1938, Aug. 30, 1939, Nov. 13, 1941, Apr. 16, 1945, July 6, 1945, Apr. 10, 1946, Jan. 8, 1948, May 9, 1949, Mar. 20, 1952
Shields Francis J
May 7, 1951
Sittler, Edward L.
Dec. 21, 1951
Smith, Harold Dewey, 1898-1947.
Feb. 18, 1942, Feb. 24, 1942
Smith, H. Alexander (Howard Alexander), 1880-1966
June 21, 1949
Smith, Margaret (Chase), 1897-
Jan. 10, 1952
Snyder, John W. (John Wesley), 1895-1985
Dec. 14, 1948
Somervell, Brehon Burke, 1892-1955.
Aug.4, 1942, Feb. 7, 1944
Sparkman, John, 1899-1985
May 9, 1951, June 15, 1951, July 3, 1951, July 5, 1951, Oct. 26, 1951, Jan. 9, 1952, Jan. 11, 1952, Jan. 17, 1952, Jan. 29, 1952, June 13, 1952, June 20, 1952
Staebler, Neil, 1905-
May 1951-Nov. 1952
Symington, Stuart, 1901-
Jan. 15, 1952
Taft, Charles Phelps, 1897-
March. 25, 1936, Feb. 15, 1945
Taft, Robert A. (Robert Alphonso), 1889-1953.
April 15, 1947
Thomas, Elbert Duncan, 1883-1953.
Aug. 30. 1951
Tito, Josip Broz, 1892-1980.
Aug. 17, 1951 [memo] recording a conversation between Tito and Moody
Townsend, Francis E. (Francis Everett), 1867-1960.
June 11, 1951
Transportation
Harvey Fruehauf, May 10, 1938, concerning wage rates and competition in the trucking industry
Truman, Harry S., 1884-1972.
Aug. 17, 1951, June 11, 1952 [encl.], July 10, 1952
U.S. Department of State
Ben Crosby, July 15, 1952, discussing banning of the U.S.S.R. information bulletins in the United States
U.S. Economic Cooperation Administration
Milton Katz, Aug. 13, 1951, on the Economic Cooperation Administration
U.S. Temporary National Economy Committee.
Ruth Aull, July 7, 1941 (encl.)
U.S. Tennessee Valley Authority.
May 21, 1951
Union of Soviet Socialist Republics.
Ben Crosby, July 15, 1952, discussing banning of the U.S.S.R. Information Bulletins in the United States
Vandenberg, Arthur H. (Arthur Hendrick), 1884-1951.
May 12, 1936, Sept. 16, 1944, Nov. 23, 1945, Dec. 28, 1946, May 23, 1949, Jan. 25, 1950
Van Wagoner, Murray Delos, 1898-
Apr. 8, 1952
Voorhis, Jerry, 1901-
Oct. 17, 1941, Oct. 28, 1941, Nov. 25, 1945
Wagner, Robert F. (Robert Ferdinand), 1877-1953.
July 30, 1935
Warren, Earl, 1891-1974.
Mar. 16, 1947
Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-
Apr. 1951-Nov. 1952
Willkie, Wendell L. (Wendell Lewis), 1892-1944.
Nov. 28, 1942, Dec. 11, 1942, Apr. 6, 1943, Apr. 19, 1943, Aug. 26, 1943, Nov. 3, 1943, Dec. 20, 1943
Wilson, Charles Erwin, 1890-1961.
Apr. 16, 1942
Wolcott, Jesse Paine, 1893-1969.
Apr. 12, 1938, Jan. 12, 1939, Oct. 7, 1942